<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Home on DIVYA RAKHIANI</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Home on DIVYA RAKHIANI</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 16 Dec 2018 22:34:04 +0100</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>WHO AM I ?</title>
      <link>/sections/simple-values/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/sections/simple-values/</guid>
      <description>Divya is an Agile enthusiast, technical tester and a teacher at heart!
1.) Inception expert – Divya can facilitate workshops to help build product canvas by defining user journeys and personas. She has experience collaborating with UX Designers, Developers and Business Analysts on such workshops.
2.) Industry Experience – Divya is a Tester with 8+ years of industry experience working in an Agile environment. She has hands-on experience in all stages of software testing life cycle from the White box, Black box, Automation testing to Regression and Usability testing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>WORK EXPERIENCE</title>
      <link>/sections/simple-choices/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/sections/simple-choices/</guid>
      <description> BEANWORKS , Senior Lead QA Engineer July 2019 -Present THOUGHTWORKS , Senior Consultant August 2016 - June 2019 DELL EMC , Software Quality Engineer November 2013 - August 2016 INFOSYS , Systems Engineer October 2011 - October 2013 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>/sections/simple-people/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/sections/simple-people/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/about/</guid>
      <description>Divya Rakhiani has more than 8 years of experience in Quality Assurance working in a startup like Beanworks, Service companies like Infosys and Thoughtworks and Product companies like Dell EMC. She currently heads the Quality Engineering department at a startup called Beanworks that specializes in automating the tedious and paper-heavy accounting process. It’s rated the 13th best startup in the Vancouver tech market. Divya sees herself today as a new immigrant to Canada and is building her career helping QA teams to use technologies like UI automation using cypress/selenium, test stabilization pipelines, and CI/CD for each code deployment.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>WHAT I WISH TO DO?</title>
      <link>/sections/simple/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/sections/simple/</guid>
      <description>Talk, discuss and work on everything that involves software testing, agile practices, DevOps and Automation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Talks &amp; Conferences</title>
      <link>/speaking_experience/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/speaking_experience/</guid>
      <description>1.) XCONF,Gurgaon,September 2016  Topic: Let&amp;rsquo;s implement test pyramid Speakers: Divya Rakhiani and Hanika Chauhan Talk summary: This was a 30 min lightning talk about implementing the test pyramid on a weather application. The goal of the talk was to advocate writing limited end to end tests as they are expensive and maintenance heavy.   2.) VodQa meetup,Gurgaon,May 2018  Topic: Test strategy with Micro services(Contract Testing and Service Virtualization) Speakers: Divya Rakhiani and Ishaan Madaan Talk summary : This was a 2-hour hands-on workshop to educate the participants about the concept of Contract testing using the tool PACT.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>If Halsey was a QA.... </title>
      <link>/posts/bad-architects/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Dec 2018 22:34:04 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/bad-architects/</guid>
      <description>I wrote a RAP song about QAing .. because why not ??
click here to read</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>